Gather round, come take a look...
It's time for Theatre of Darkness.
Solution
This is the story of a certain police officer working at a police box...
Hm? Why is there a doll in a place like that?
Senior, thanks for your hard work!
Good work.
Hey,
at the intersection on 4th Street,
there was a doll left.
Ah,
Senior, you were just off shift,
so you probably don't know.
Two days ago,
There was an accident involving a child.
It seems the mother suffered a mental breakdown from the shock
and was wandering around that area for a while.
She might have left it behind.
That doll...
May I ask for your name?
Do you
live around here?
Could she be hard of hearing...?
Where did you get that doll—
This child isn't a doll.
Oh, I see...
Man, what a mess...
Senior, were you talking to someone just now?
Ah, well, this old lady...
An old lady?
Huh?
Where did she go?
Must be nice...
I've always wanted to try ventriloquism with something like this.
What are you talking about?
That's lost property.
Whatever you do, don't take it home with you.
Understood.
Alright, I'm heading home then.
Got it, good work!
Give the child back!
There's no one here...
I'm home.
Hmm...
That must have hurt...
You poor thing...
Honoka, who are you talking to?
A friend!
EH!
Wh-Hey!
This...
Where did you get that?!
When I came back from grocery shopping,
it was left right in front of the entrance.
Taro-chan,
got into a fight with his friends!
St-Stop that right now!
Dear!
Why would you do something so awful?!
A-Anyway,
this doll is bad news!
Taro-chan isn't a doll!
That's right!
What??
It hurt...
N-No, stop!
You guys!
Wh-What's wrong with you?!
Big brother,
don't get in my way!
Good morning.
Huh, is Senior Takeuchi taking the day off today as well?
Ah, good morning.
Yeah, that seems to be the case.
By the way,
our traffic safety instruction at the elementary school,
is next week, right?
I'm Officer Hatanaka.
And this here is my friend...
Taro-chan.
Today, Taro-chan
is going to talk to everyone about how to ride a bicycle!
Whoa, really?!
THE END.